I told you that the infected data was sent to the market only yesterday,
some reaction was received yesterday, maybe
some reaction will be received today also, hence let's take
a look from Parthiv on non-life insurance companies,
that data will also be displayed on your screen,
Parthiv, you are looking at some company,
in this you are feeling that it is better here
and there is a trade or some value based investment,
actually
good morning everyone, see insurance because insurance
basement knows that the
protection gap in life insurance is
still very high, which goes to show that
they are recently inside the benefit and there is one
data point which we have seen that it always
hits one correct insurance
penetration always increases when capital
income increases and India is only crossing
$2000, this is a very important instruction
point because going beyond $2000, it is going to reach
$10000 in 10 years, 15 years,
so taking that into account, in whichever countries
this special cross has happened, we have seen that  The
savings pool towards insurance
or protection is always less,
so what kind of industry is this
where there are organized players and
where there are market leaders and
we have already seen a lot of confusion in this industry,
so names like HDFC
and the value of new business margins are also there,
we have seen that in the past, which they used to do
around 16-18, now it has become an
new name of doing anywhere above
22% and HDFC Life, this
company has always been innovative in terms
of introducing new products, yes, if
we look at the month and month, sometimes the data will be
long because there is seasonality
in this statement, but I think despite the challenge coming
from the budget, I think
this company has mitigated its business model very well, so
in life insurance, our most preferred choice will be
HDFC Life, which is getting 3.2 times the
price to value, which is not only this, if we compare it
with global peers
playing global companies.  I don't guarantee growth till 15,
even in the coming 10 years, that is
in HDFC Life, secondly in the non-life space,
in general insurance, we are finding ESIC
Lambert very good, no doubt complete
and comment ratio has been around 104 103,
but our sir believes that you have
integration of inorganic acid, now
these two-three sirs have commented ratio
towards
100%, so the growth trends that are showing from the brother
and the company focusing and non-
competitive and high margin segment, so
here we are feeling that the help
segment is a big statement, this can be completely, so
ICC loudspection
ok, two are
more liked in their life and this almost
hi pay has also been banded yesterday Sony